Izzy: Well, what do you want to see?
Ben: I want to see the real London.
What size is this shirt?
Assistant: Let’s see.
It’s a small.
Ben: Listen, Izzy. My photography class has a little show next week.
Do you want to come?
Izzy: I’d love to come. Thanks.
Izzy: Come in?
Pamela: Hi, Izzy.
Here’s a parcel that came for you.
Izzy: Thanks.
Pamela: You’re welcome.
Oh, I’m tired today.
Izzy, you look worried.
Izzy: Do I?
Pamela: Yes, you do.
Is everything OK?
Izzy: Yes…No. I have a friend.
He’s a photographer and he has his show today.
Pamela: A friend?
Izzy: Yes. His name is Ben.
Pamela: Ben. A good strong name. I like the name.
Izzy: And he’s a really nice guy, but…
Pamela: But?
Izzy: He goes to Tensquare School of Photography.
Pamela: Ah.
Izzy: So I don’t know…I don’t really want to go back there.
It was not a good time for me at that school.
Pamela: I remember, Izzy.
Izzy: But I really want to see Ben’s show…
Pamela: Yes, well…if you like this boy, then go.
Izzy: I think I like him.
Pamela: Either you like him, or you don’t.
Izzy: Yes…I like him.
Pamela: Then go to his show!
Don’t worry about the past.
Izzy: Hey, Mr Fischer.
Ben: Hi, Izzy. How are you?
Izzy: I’m good.
Ben: Can you still come tonight?
Izzy: Of course.
I really want to see your show.
Ben: OK, cool. So it’s at the Click Gallery.
Do you know where that is?
Izzy: No, but I’m sure I can find it. Don’t worry.
Ben: OK, great.
See you later.
Izzy: See you.